fifamedicinediploma.com 2017-06-10

# Privacy Policy | FIFA Diploma in Football Medicine

For any definition used in this Privacy Policy, please refer to the FIFA Terms and Conditions. Please read the following to learn more about FIFA’s Privacy Policy and the ways in which FIFA use your information before you proceed with use of the FIFAmedicinediploma.com Website.

_Date of issue of this Privacy Policy: 01.04.2017_

**International Transfer**

YOUR INFORMATION IS COLLECTED AND PROCESSED IN SWITZERLAND, AND MAY BE TRANSFERRED, STORED AND USED ELSEWHERE DEPENDING ON THE LOCATION OF THE AFFILIATES, BUSINESS PARTNERS, AND OTHER ENTITIES WHO ARE PERMITTED TO ACCESS SUCH INFORMATION UNDER THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY (AND SUCH LOCATIONS MAY INCLUDE COUNTRIES WHICH MAY NOT AFFORD THE SAME LEVEL OF PROTECTION OF SUCH DATA AS THE COUNTRY FROM WHICH YOU PROVIDED THE INFORMATION). BY ACCESSING OR USING THE FIFAmedicinediploma.com WEBSITE OR SUBMITTING PERSONAL INFORMATION TO FIFA YOU SPECIFICALLY AGREE TO SUCH PROCESSING AND TRANSFER.

**The collection of information and how FIFA uses it**

The main reason why FIFA collects information is to provide you with the Services you request; to manage your account; and to enable you to enjoy and easily navigate the FIFAmedicinediploma.com Website.

FIFA uses the information about you for the following general purposes: to provide you with the Services you request; to manage your account, to communicate with you in general; to respond to your questions and comments; to invite you to participate in surveys; to notify you about special offers that may be of interest to you; to enable FIFA to check the usage of the FIFAmedicinediploma.com Website and its effectiveness as a communications tool and to ensure that you do not miss important communications intended for you; to help FIFA determine how to improve the FIFAmedicinediploma.com Website; to prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities and to help ensure that only authorised parties are accessing the FIFAmedicinediploma.com Website using your user login and password; to enforce the FIFA Terms & Conditions and the relevant Privacy Policy available on the FIFAmedicinediploma.com Website; to process your information to provide you with educational, medical and event related information as well as for customisation of the Service and as otherwise described to you at the point of collection.

**The information FIFA collects from you**

FIFA collects information when you register for an account, when you use the FIFAmedicinediploma.com Website and when you enter into transactions, promotions or sweepstakes. The information collected may include but is not limited to the following personal information: email address, last name, first name, country of residence, date of birth, gender, screen name, password, course and quiz progress.

**The processing of data**

The data will be processed and stored on servers in Switzerland. It will be kept as long as necessary to fulfill the purpose(s) for which it was submitted and will be erased at the latest upon closure of the account.

**Cookies**

When you visit the FIFAmedicinediploma.com Website, FIFA will use “cookies” to collect certain information about you. Cookies are small data files which are transferred to your computer’s hard disk in order to memorize information like registration IDs and passwords. A cookie will typically contain the name of the domain from which the cookie has originated, the “lifetime” of the cookie and various values.

FIFA further utilizes session ID cookies to enable certain features of the FIFAmedicinediploma.com Website, to better understand how you interact with the FIFAmedicinediploma.com Website and to monitor aggregate usage by FIFAmedicinediploma.com Websites’ users and web traffic routing on the FIFAmedicinediploma.com Website. Session ID cookies are, unlike persistent cookies, deleted from your computer when you log off from the FIFAmedicinediploma.com Website and close your browser.

Please note that you can always choose to block cookies by updating your Web browser privacy settings.

To do so, you will have to access the “Help” menu in your browser’s menu bar and search for the term “cookies”. Please however take note that if you block cookies, you may not be able to use all sections of the FIFAmedicinediploma.com Website or all functionality of the Services.

Other third parties that are presenting advertisements on or within the FIFAmedicinediploma.com Website may also set and use cookies to access your computer. Please refer specifically to each third party website and statements of privacy to understand their procedures for collecting, using and disclosing personal information through their cookies.

**Automatic Information**

FIFA automatically asks for some information about your computer when you visit the FIFAmedicinediploma.com Website, regardless of whether you have registered for an account or not by just browsing FIFA’s servers.

FIFA do not collect any data automatically.

**Phishing**

Identity theft and the practice currently known as “phishing” are of great concern to FIFA. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your account ID, login password or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

FIFA may send information about you to third parties when:

  1. a) FIFA has your consent to share the information; or
  2. b) FIFA needs to share your information to provide you with access to the FIFAmedicinediploma.com Website; or
  3. c) FIFA needs to share your information to fulfill your requests for any Services made through the FIFAmedicinediploma.com Website by you; or
  4. d) FIFA provides the information to companies who work on behalf of FIFA under agreements; or
  5. e) FIFA responds to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or
  6. f) FIFA believes it is necessary, as determined in FIFA s’ sole discretion, to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, emergency situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of FIFAs’ Terms and Conditions, to protect the rights of FIFA, FIFA or its affiliates or as otherwise required by law.

**Security**

FIFA wants you to feel confident about using the FIFAmedicinediploma.com Website. For that reason, FIFA has implemented reasonable technical and organizational measures designed to secure your information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, the Internet is an open system and FIFA cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat those measures or use your information for improper purposes.

If you communicate with FIFA by email, you should note that the secrecy of Internet email is uncertain. By sending sensitive or confidential email messages or information which are not encrypted you accept the risk of such uncertainty and possible lack of confidentiality over the Internet.

**Your right to access information**

You are entitled to see the information held about you. If you wish to do this, please use the Feedback contact form at www.FIFAmedicinediploma.com. FIFA may require you to provide verification of your identity and to pay an administration fee to provide a copy of the information we hold. Please note that in certain circumstances FIFA may withhold access to your information where FIA have the right to do so under current data protection legislation.

**Updating/deleting your information**

You may review, correct, update, change or delete your personal information at any time by accessing your account on the FIFAmedicinediploma.com Website. FIFA will accommodate your request for deletion, if FIFA do not have any legal obligation to retain the record (for logged in Users: http://FIFAmedicinediploma.com/your-profile/).

**Waiver**

You herewith unconditionally and irrevocably waive any and all claims against FIFA, its officers, directors, employees, representatives, affiliates, auxiliaries and partners resulting from any decision in connection with the submitted data. The processing of the personal data shall not exceed the scope described or implied herein.

**Links to other sites**

If any part of the FIFAmedicinediploma.com Website link to other websites, those websites do not operate under this Privacy Policy. If you choose to visit an advertiser or click on another third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s website. FIFA does not exercise control over third party websites and therefore recommend you examine the privacy statements posted on these other websites to understand their procedures for collecting, using and disclosing personal information.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy may be amended from time to time. If FIFA amends this Privacy Policy, FIFA shall place an updated version on this page of the FIFAmedicinediploma.com Website. You will have to accept and agree to be bound by any updated version in order to continue using the FIFAmedicinediploma.com Website and its Services.

**Applicable law and arbitration**

This Privacy Policy and all matters arising out of or related to this Privacy Policy shall be governed exclusively by the substantive laws of Switzerland.

All disputes in connection with this Privacy Policy are to be promptly settled between the parties by negotiation. If no solution can be reached, such disputes shall, to the exclusion of any court or other forum, be exclusively resolved by an arbitral tribunal consisting of three (3) arbitrators under the auspices of, and pursuant to, the Swiss Rules of International Arbitration of the Swiss Chambers of Commerce. The seat of the arbitration shall be Zurich, Switzerland and the language of the proceedings shall be English. For the avoidance of any doubt, any determination made by the arbitral tribunal shall be final and binding on the parties.
